Guide to the Pierre Jay Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Documents, Series IV
  - Doc. 173: Finances of the Reich Tax Reductions, March, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - Doc. 174: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank February 28, 1926, March, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Doc. 175: Tax Receipts of the Reich February, 1926, March, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Doc. 176: Movement of Funds at the Reichshauptkasse February, 1926, March, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Doc. 177: The Situation in Germany, March, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 166)
  - Doc. 178: Finances of the Reich: Financial Statistics for the States and the Communes, March, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Doc. 179: Reparation Payments and Foreign Credits, March, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - Doc. 180: Finances of the Reich: Memorandum on the Loans of the Reich for 1925, March, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Doc. 181: Position of the Public Debt of the Reich, January 31, 1926, April, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Doc. 182: Reduction in Taxation, April, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Doc. 183: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank, March 31, 1926, April, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Doc. 184: Report of the Deutsche Rentenbank for 1925, March, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - Doc. 185: Report of the Deutsche Rentenbank-Kreditanstalt August 5 - December 31, 1925, April, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - Doc. 186: Report of the Deutsche Bank for the Year 1925, April, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 175)
  - Doc. 188: Tax Receipts of the Reich for March 1926 and the Financial Year 1925-1926, April, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 176)
  - Doc. 189: Position of the German Public Debt February 28, 1926, April, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - Doc. 190: Movement of Funds at the Reichshauptkasse March 1926 and the Financial Year 1925-1926, April, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - Doc. 191: Second Decree of May 7, 1926 Concerning the Reimbursement of the Reparation Duty, May, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Doc. 192: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank April 30, 1926, May, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 180)
  - Doc. 193: Tax Receipts of the Reich April, 1926, May, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - Doc. 194: Position of the Public Debt of the Reich March 31, 1926, May, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - Doc. 195: Revenue and Expenditure of the Reich April, 1926, June, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - Doc. 196: Finances of the Reich: Modifications in Tax on Automobiles and Cigarettes, June, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - Doc 197: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank May 31, 1926, June, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - Doc. 198: Finances of the Reich: Revenues from Taxation for May 1926, June, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - Doc. 199: Finances of the Reich State of the Public Debt on April 30, 1926, June, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - Doc. 200: Finances of the Reich, Receipts and Payments of the Reich for the First two Months of 1926-1927, July, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - Doc. 201: Finances of the Reich, Position of the Public Debt, May 31, 1926, July, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - Doc. 203: Finances of the Reich. Revenue from Taxation June, 1926, July, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Doc. 204: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich - First Quarter of 1926-1927 (Box 9, Folder 191)
  - Doc. 205: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank July 31, 1926, August, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 192)
  - Doc. 206: Finances of the Reich: Tac Receipts for July, 1926, August, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 193)
  - Doc. 207: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich in July, 1926, September, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 194)
  - Doc. 208: Insurance in Germany Against Export Credit Risks With Financial Support from The Reich, September, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 195)
  - Doc. 209: Finances of the Reich. Position of the Public Debt, June 30 and July 31, 1926, September, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 196)
  - Doc. 210: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank, August 31, 1926, September, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 197)
  - Doc. 211: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts For August, 1926, September, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 198)
  - Doc. 212: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich in August, 1926, October, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 199)
  - Doc. 213: Finances of the Reich. Position of the Public Debt of the Reich. August 31, 1926, October, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 200)
  - Doc. 214: Finances of the Reich. Tax Receipts September, 1926, October, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 201-A)
  - Doc. 215: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank September 30, 1926, October, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 201-B)
  - Doc. 216: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich September, 1926, November, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 202)
  - Doc. 217: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank October 31, 1926, November, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 203)
  - Doc. 218: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts for October, 1926, November, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 204)
  - Doc. 219: Finances of the Reich: Position of the Public Debt of the Reich, September 30, 1926, November, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 205)
  - Doc. 220: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments in October, 1926, December, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Doc. 221: Finances of the Reich: Position of the Public Debt as at October 31, 1926, December, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 207)
  - Doc. 222: Finances of the Reich: Statements of the Finance Minister of the Reich on the Budget Situation and the Prospects of a Loan., December, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Doc. 223: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts For November, 1926, December, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Doc. 224: Public Finance: Exceptional Grants For Christmas, December, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Doc. 225: Berlin Chamber of Commerce on the Economic Year 1926, January, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 211)
  - Doc. 226: Finances of the Reich: State of the Public Debt on November 30, 1926, January, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 212)
  - Doc. 227: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at November 30, 1926, January, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 213)
  - Doc. 227: [Duplicate] Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at November 30, 1926, January, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 214)
  - Doc. 228: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at December 31, 1926, January, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 215)
  - Doc. 229: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich in November 1926, January, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 216)
  - Doc. 230: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts for December 1926, January, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 217)
  - Doc. 231: Jurisdiction and Activities of the Advisory office for Foreign Loans, January, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 218)
  - Doc. 232: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich in December, 1926, February, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 219)
  - Doc. 233: The Production of the Contributions in Respect of Reparations, February, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 220)
  - Doc 234: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at January 31, 1927, February, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 221)
  - Doc. 235: Finances of the Reich: Public Debt as at December 31, 1926, February, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 222)
  - Doc. 236: Finances of the Reich: Speech by the Finance Minister on the Budget for 1927 and the Financial Position, February 16, 1927, February, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 223)
  - Doc. 237: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts for January 1927, February, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 224)
  - Doc. 238: Finances of the Reich: Resumé of speech by Finance Minister, February, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 225)
  - Doc. 239: Finances of the Reich: Resumé of The second speech of the Finance Minister, February, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Doc. 240: Finances of the Reich: Simplified Tax Collection and Extended Jurisdiction of the Finanzämter, March, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Doc. 241: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at February 38, 1927, March 9, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Doc. 242: Finances of the Reich: Public Debt as at January 31, 1927, March, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 229)
  - Doc. 243: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich, January, 1927, March, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 230)
  - Doc. 244: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts for February, 1927, March, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 231)
  - Doc. 245: Annual Report of the Reichsbank for 1926, March, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 232)
  - Doc. 246: Report of the Deutsche Bank for the Year 1926, March, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 233)
  - Doc. 247: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich in February, 1927, April, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 234)
  - Doc. 248: Finances of the Reich: Public Debt as at February 38, 1927, April, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 235)
  - Doc. 249: Report of the Deutsche Rentenbank for 1926, April, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 236)
  - Doc. 250: Management and Business Report of the Deutsche Rentenbank Kreditanstalt, April, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 237)
  - Doc. 251: The Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as of March 31, 1927, April, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  - Doc. 252: Tax Receipts of the Reich for March 1927 and for Financial Year 1926-1927, April, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 239)
  - Doc. 253: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich for March, 1927 and for the Year 1926-1927, May, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 240)
  - Doc. 254: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as on April 30, 1927, May, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  - Doc. 255: Tax Receipts of the Reich for April 1927, May, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 242)
  - Doc. 256: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at May 31, 1927, June, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 243)
  - Doc. 257: Tax Receipts of the Reich for the Month of May 1927, June, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  - Doc. 258: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich for April 1927, June, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 245)
  - Doc. 259: Finance of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich in May 1927, July, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 246)
  - Doc. 260: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as on June 30, 1927, July, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 247)
  - Doc. 261: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts of the Reich for the month of June, 1927, July, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 248)
  - Doc. 262: Finances of the Reich: Position of the Public Debt of the Reich as at June 30, 1927, August, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 249)
  - Doc. 263: Balance sheet of the Rentenbank as on July 31, 1927, August, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 250)
  - Doc. 264: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich in June, 1927, August, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 251)
  - Doc. 265: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts of the Reich for July 1927, September, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 252)
  - Doc. 266: Balance Shet of the Rentenbank as on August 31, 1927, September, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 253)
  - Doc. 267: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts of the Reich for August, 1927, September, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 254)
  - Doc. 268: Finances of the Reich: Alterations in the Sugar and Alcohol Taxes., October, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 255)
  - [BLANK] (Box 10, Folder 256)
  - Doc. 269: Finances of the Reich: Public Debt of the Reich as at August 31, 1927, October, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 257)
  - Doc. 270: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich in July and August, 1927, October, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 258)
  - Doc. 271: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as on September 30, 1927, October, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 259)
  - Doc. 272: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts of the Reich for September, 1927, October, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 260)
  - Doc. 273: Finances of the Reich: Public Debt of the Reich as at September 30, 1927, November, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - Doc. 274: Text of the New Directives for the Advisory Office, November, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - Doc. 275: Tax Receipts of the Reich for October 1927, November, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 263)
  - Doc. 276: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank October 31, 1927, November, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 264)
  - Doc. 277: Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank November 30, 1927, December, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 265)
  - Doc. 278: Finances of the Reich: Tax Receipts For November, 1927, January, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 266)
  - Doc. 279: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments of the Reich for September, 1927 and for the first six months of 1927-1928, January, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 267)
  - Doc. 280: Finances of the Reich: Amendment of the Income Tax [Tax on Wages and General Tax], January, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - Doc. 281: Finances of the Reich: Receipts and Payments for October and November, 1927, January, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - Doc. 282: Finances of the Reich: Speech by the Finance Minister, Dr. Koehler, on the Budget for 1928, January 19, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 270)
  - Doc. 283: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at December 31, 1927, January, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 271)
  - Doc. 284: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at January 31, 1928, February 18, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 272)
  - Doc. 285: Annual Report of the Reichsbank for the Year 1927, March, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 273)
  - Doc. 286: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at February, 29, 1928, March, 1928 (Box 10, Folder 274)
  - Doc. 287: Report of the Deutsche Bank for the Year 1927, March 22, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 275)
  - Doc. 288: Report of the Golddiskontbank for 1927, March, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 276)
  - Doc. 289: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at March 31, 1928, April 1928 (Box 11, Folder 277)
  - Doc. 290: Report of the Deutsche Rentenbank for 1927, April, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 278)
  - Doc. 291: Management and Business Report of the Deutsche Rentenbank-Kreditanstalt 1927, April, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 279)
  - Doc. 292: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at April 30, 1928, May, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 280)
  - Doc. 293: Report of the German Railway Co. for the Third Business Year, 1927, May, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 281)
  - Doc. 293-A: Report of the German Railway Co. for the Third Business Year - 1927 cont. Doc. 293, May, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 282)
  - Doc. 294: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at May 1928, June, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 283)
  - Doc. 295: Germany's Economic Development During first half of the Year 1928, July, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 284)
  - Doc 296: Programme of New German Government Address of Chancellor Before Rekhstag, July, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 285)
  - Doc. 297: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at June 30, 1928, July, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 286)
  - Doc. 298: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at July 31, 1928, August, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - Doc. 299: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at August 31, 1928, September, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Doc. 300: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at September 30, 1928, October, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 289)
  - Doc. 301: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at October 31, 1928, November, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Doc. 302: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at November 30, 1928, December, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - Doc. 303: Germany's Economic Position at the of the Year 1928-1929, January, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 292)
  - Doc. 304: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at December 31, 1928, January, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - Doc. 305: Annual Report of the Reichsbank for the Year 1928, February, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Doc. 306: The Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at January 31, 1929, February, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - Doc. 307: Budget of the Reich for 1929-1930, March, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 296)
  - Doc. 308: Finances of the Reich: Speech by Finance Minsiter of the Reich, Dr. Hilferding, March, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Doc. 309: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at February 28, 1929, March, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 298)
  - Doc. 310: Report of the Deutsche Rentenbank for 1928, March, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 299)
  - Doc. 311: Management and Business Report of the Deutsche Rentanbank-Kreditanstalt - 4th Business Year 1928, March, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 300)
  - Doc. 312: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at March 31, 1929, April, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 301)
  - Doc. 313: Monthly Balance Sh-et of the Rentenbank as at April 30, 1929, May, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 302)
  - Doc. 314: Report of the German Railway Co. for the Fourth Business Year 1928, June, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 303)
  - Doc. 315: The Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at May 31, 1929, June, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 304)
  - Doc. 316: Germany's Economic Position in the first half of 1929, July, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 305)
  - Doc. 317: The Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at June 30, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 306)
  - Doc. 318: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at July 31, 1929, August, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - Doc. 319: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at August 31, 1929, September, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 308)
  - Doc. 320: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at September, 1929, October, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 309)
  - Doc. 323: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at November, 1929, December, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 310)
  - Doc. 324: Financial Programme of Reich Government, December, 1929 (Box 11, Folder 311)
  - Doc. 326: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at December 31, 1929, January, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 312)
  - Doc. 328: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at January 31, 1930, February, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 313)
  - Doc. 329: Reichstag Speech of the Chancellor of the Reich Herr Mueller, March 12, 1930, March, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 314)
  - Doc. 330: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at February 38, 1930, March, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 315)
  - Doc. 331: Annual Report of the Deutsche Rentenbank for 1929, March, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 316)
  - Doc. 333: Reichstag Speech of the Chancellor of the Reich, Dr. Brüning, April 1, 1930, April, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 317)
  - Doc 334: Monthly Balance Sheet of the Rentenbank as at March 31, 1930, April, 1930 (Box 11, Folder 318)
- Materials r.e. Meetings of the Transfer Committee, Series V
  - Minutes
    - First year: meetings 1-11, 1924 October-1925 August (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Second year: meetings 12-20, 1925 September-1926 August (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Third year: meetings 21-31, 1926 September-1927 August (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Fourth year: meetings 22-40, 1927 September-1928 August (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Agendas
    - 24th meeting, 1927 January 29 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 25th meeting, 1927 February 26 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 26th meeting, 1927 March 28 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 27th meeting, 1927 April 30 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 28th meeting, 1927 May 24 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 29th meeting, 1927 June 25 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 30th meeting, 1927 July 30 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 31st meeting, 1927 August 27 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 32nd meeting, 1927 September 30 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - 33rd meeting, 1927 October 28 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - 34th meeting, 1927 November 28 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - 35th meeting, 1928 January 28 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - 36th meeting, 1928 February 27 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - 37th meeting, 1928 March 31 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - 38th meeting, 1928 May 10 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - 39th meeting, 1928 June 16 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - 40th meeting, 1928 July 17 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - 41st meeting, 1928 August 18 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - 42nd meeting, 1928 September 29 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - 43rd meeting, 1928 October 27 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - 44th meeting, 1928 December 22 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - 45th meeting, 1929 January 29 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - 46th meeting, 1929 February 23 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - 47th meeting, 1929 March 28 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 48th meeting, 1929 April 24 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - 49th meeting, 1929 May 23 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - 50th meeting, 1929 June 26 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - 51st meeting, 1929 July 27 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - 52nd meeting, 1929 August 24 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - 53rd meeting, 1929 September 27 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - 54th meeting, 1929 October 26 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - 55th meeting, 1929 December 14 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - 56th A meeting, 1930 February 21 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - 56th B meeting, 1930 February 21 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Printed Materials, Series VI
  - Annual Reports of the Reichsbank for, 1925, 1927, 1928, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Reports of the Expert Committees Appointed by the Reparation Commission, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Agent General for Reparation Payments, July, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Clauses de Réparation et Clauses Financières du Traité de Versailles annotées à la date du 1er Juillet 1927, July, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Reparation Commission: Annual Report on the Powers Accounts as at 31 August, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - League of Nations: Memorandum on Public Finance 1922-1926, 1927 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Final Act of the Hague Conference, January, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets on the German Economy, 1928, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "The Economic Forces of the World" by the Dresdner Bank, Berlin, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Bulletin of the Bank of Poland No's 2, 3, 4, 8, 1928, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "France and her capacity to Pay" by Henry Berenger, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The Bank of Japan: Annual Report for 1929, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Monthly Review of the Economic Situation in Denmark, September, October, November, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - German Tax Laws, July, August, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Documents of the Reparation Commission re: Implementation of the Hague Agreement of January 20, 1930, May, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Summary of German Press, September 16/17, 192 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - "Potentialities of the Young Plan" by F. Stallforth (Box 22, Folder 17)